Guide to the Records of the Women's Bureau of the U.S. Department of Labor, Pt.2, Series A on Microfilm, 1918-1965
Records of the Women's Bureau of the U.S. Department of Labor, Pt.2, Series A on Microfilm.
- Agreement between the American Leather Products Corporation and the International Union, UAW-CIO, Local 226., 1943; 42 (Reel 2)
  June 1943. 5 frames.
- Automatic Products Company of Milwaukee, WI., 1944; 43 (Reel 3)
  July 6, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 3 frames.
- Globe Union, Inc. of Milwaukee, WI., 1944; 44 (Reel 3)
  July 22, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 3 frames.
- Harley-Davidson of Milwaukee, WI., 1944; 45 (Reel 3)
  July 22, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 4 frames.
- Briggs and Stratton Corporation of Milwaukee, WI., 1944; 46 (Reel 3)
  July 29, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 2 frames.
- Rockola Manufacturing Corporation of Chicago, IL., 1944; 47 (Reel 3)
  August 28, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 3 frames.
- General Electric X-Ray Corporation of Chicago, IL., 1944; 48 (Reel 3)
  August 29, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 3 frames.
- S. Buchsbaum and Company of Chicago, IL., 1944; 49 (Reel 3)
  August 27, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 2 frames.
- Howard Foundry Company of Chicago, IL., 1944; 50 (Reel 3)
  August 30, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 3 frames.
- Universal Castings Corporation of Chicago, IL., 51 (Reel 3)
  n.d. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 1 frame.
- Minneapolis-Honeywell Regulator Company of Chicago, IL., 1944; 52 (Reel 3)
  September 8, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 4 frames.
- Revere Copper and Brass, Inc., Ordnance Division, of Chicago, IL., 1944; 53 (Reel 3)
  September 15, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 2 frames.
- Continental Roll and Steel Foundry Company of East Chicago, IL., 1944; 54 (Reel 3)
  September 29, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 3 frames.
- Lion Manufacturing Company of Chicago, IL., 1944; 55 (Reel 3)
- Automatic Electric Company-Lion Manufacturing Company of Chicago, IL., 1944; 56 (Reel 3)
  September 15, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 3 frames.
- American Phenolic Corporation of Cicero, IL., 1944; 57 (Reel 3)
- Allen-Bradley Company of Milwaukee, WI., 1944; 58 (Reel 3)
  July 1, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 3 frames.
- Wrought Washer Manufacturing Company of Milwaukee, WI., 1944; 59 (Reel 3)
  July 29, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 3 frames.
- George J. Meyer Manufacturing Company of Milwaukee, WI., 1944; 60 (Reel 3)
- Carnegie Illinois Steel Corporation of Chicago, IL., 1944; 61 (Reel 3)
  October 6, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case.
- International Harvester Company of East Moline, IL., 1943; 62 (Reel 3)
  December 9, 1943. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 2 frames.
- John Deere Plow Company of Moline, IL., 1943; 63 (Reel 3)
  December 1943. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 1 frame.
- Feltex Corporation of Rock Island, IL., 1943; 64 (Reel 3)
  December 8, 1943. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 2 frames.
- Union Malleable Iron Works of the Deere Company of East Moline, IL., 1943; 65 (Reel 3)
  December 11, 1943. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 2 frames.
- International Harvester Company of East Moline, IL., 1943; 66 (Reel 3)
- Minneapolis-Moline Power Implement Company of Moline, IL., 1943; 67 (Reel 3)
  December 14, 1943. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 2 frames.
- John Deere Harvester Works of East Moline, IL., 1943; 68 (Reel 3)
  December 10, 1943. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 2 frames.
- Eagle Signal Corporation of Moline, IL., 1943; 69 (Reel 3)
- J.I. Case, Rock Island Works of Rock Island, IL., 1943; 70 (Reel 3)
  December 13, 1943. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 2 frames.
- Oakes Products Division of the Houdaille Hersey Corporation of North Chicago, IL., 1943; 71 (Reel 3)
  December 21, 1943. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 2 frames.
- Peoria Cordage Company of Peoria IL., 1944; 72 (Reel 3)
  January 4, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 2 frames.
- Peoria Malleable Company of Peoria, IL., 1944; 73 (Reel 3)
  January 5, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 2 frames.
- Caterpillar Tractor Company of Peoria, IL., 1944; 74 (Reel 3)
  January 4, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 3 frames.
- Altofer Brothers of East Peoria, IL., 1944; 75 (Reel 3)
- Dole Valve Company of Chicago, IL., 1943; 76 (Reel 3)
  December 31, 1943.Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 2 frames.
- Wire Cloth Products, Inc. of Forest Park, IL., 1943; 77 (Reel 3)
  December 27, 1943. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 2 frames.
- Ingersoll Steel and Disc Division of the Borg Warner Corporation of Chicago, IL., 1944; 78 (Reel 3)
  January 29, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 1 frame.
- Industrial Camp Corporation of Chicago, IL., 1944; 79 (Reel 3)
  February 3, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 2 frames.
- Oliver Farm Equipment Company of South Bend, IN., 1944; 80 (Reel 3)
  February 14, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 2 frames.
- Excel Curtain Company of Elkhart, IN., 1944; 81 (Reel 3)
  March 11, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 2 frames.
- C.G. Conn, Ltd. of Elkhart, IN., 1944; 82 (Reel 3)
- Ball Band Plant of the US Rubber Company of Mishawaka, IN., 1944; 83 (Reel 3)
  March 18, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 2 frames.
- Women's Bureau Trade Union Survey of Local No. 226, UAW-CIO of Indianapolis, IN., 1944; 84 (Reel 3)
  March 18, 1944. 12 frames.
- American Leather Products Corporation of Indianapolis, IN., 1944; 85 (Reel 3)
- Marmon-Herrington, Inc. of Indianapolis, IN., 1944; 86 (Reel 3)
  March 18, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 3 frames.
- International Harvester Company, Foundry Unit, of Indianapolis, IN., 1944; 87 (Reel 3)
- McQuay Norris Manufacturing Company of Indianapolis, IN., 1944; 88 (Reel 3)
- Prest-O-Lite Storage Battery Corporation of Indianapolis, IN., 1944; 89 (Reel 3)
- Noblitt-Sparks Industries, Inc. of Seymour, IN., 1944; 90 (Reel 3)
  February 6, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 3 frames.
- Briggs Indiana Corporation of Evansville, IN., 1944; 91 (Reel 3)
  April 17, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 3 frames.
- Republic Aviation Corporation of Evansville, IN., 1944; 92 (Reel 3)
  April 19, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 2 frames.
- Pierce Governor Company of Anderson, IN., 1944; 93 (Reel 3)
  May 17, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 3 frames.
- Fulton Company of Milwaukee, WI., 1944; 94 (Reel 3)
  June 29, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 3 frames.
- Master Lock Company of Milwaukee, WI., 1944; 95 (Reel 3)
  June 19, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 3 frames.
- Mueller Furnace and Boiler Manufacturers of Milwaukee, WI., 1944; 96 (Reel 3)
  June 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 3 frames.
- Interviews: Women's Bureau Interview with Mr. Harry E. O'Reilly of the Chicago Federation of Labor, 1944; 97 (Reel 3)
  August 18, 1944. Regarding Employment of Women and Negroes and Equal Pay. 1 frame.
- Handwritten Note: "See Source Books Part I and II." [Reel 1, frames 0035, 0108], 98 (Reel 3)
- International Moulders and Foundry Workers Union, AF of L, Local 233., 1943; 99 (Reel 3)
  November 1, 1943. 5 frames.
- Handwritten Note: "Contract Given to Mrs. Morrison.", 100 (Reel 3)
- Agreement between the Chicago Foundrymen Association and the Chicago Conference Board of the International Moulders and Foundry Workers Union, AF of L., 1942; 101 (Reel 3)
  May 1, 1942. 4 frames.
- Handwritten Memorandum from Agnes O'Connor regarding Women's Wages in the Chicago Conference Board of the International Moulders and Foundry Workers Union, AF of L., 1943; 102 (Reel 3)
  November 4. 1943. 2 frames.
- Handwritten Notes regarding Women's Union Wages and Benefits., 1943; 103 (Reel 3)
  November 1, 1943. 4 frames.
- War Labor Board Cases., 104 (Reel 3)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local B-713, AF of L, 1943; 105 (Reel 3)
  September 17, 1943. 6 frames.
- Agreement between the Chevrolet Commercial Body Division of General Motors Corporation of Indianapolis, IN and Local 226, UAW-CIO., 1943; 43 (Reel 2)
  December 20, 1943. 1 frame.
- Agreement between Noblitt-Sparks Industries, Inc. and Local No. 97, UAW-CIO., 1944; 44 (Reel 2)
  March 27, 1944. 17 frames.
- Evansville, Indiana Plant. Special Meeting Minutes of Labor Relations Supervisor with the Plant Shop Committee., 1943; 45 (Reel 2)
  October 14, 1943. 2 frames.
- Agreement between Farm Tools, Inc., Vulcan Plow Division of Evansville, IN and Local No. 650 of the International Automobile Workers of America, AFL., 1942; 46 (Reel 2)
  May 19, 1942. 4 frames.
- Agreement between Paramount Lodge Number 1449 of District Number 90 of the International Association of Machinists and Mouldings, Inc., 1943; 47 (Reel 2)
  July 1, 1943. 9 frames.
- Agreement between Local 662, UAW-CIO and Delco-Remy Corporation., 1941; 48 (Reel 2)
  March 16, 1941. 17 frames.
- Agreement between the Ken-Rad Tube and Lamp Company of Owensboro, KY and the United Automobile Workers of America, AF of L, Local Union No. 783., 1944; 49 (Reel 2)
  May 16, 1944. 11 frames.
- Agreement between Cutler-Hammer, Inc. and the International Association of Machinists, Lodge No. 1061., 1943; 50 (Reel 2)
  July 1, 1943. 10 frames.
- Notice to Foremen from Philip Ryan, Works Manager, on the Subject of Transfers., 1943; 51 (Reel 2)
  September 23, 1943. 1 frame.
- Letter from Philip Ryan, Works Manager, regarding the Approximate Number of Women Employed in Each Department., 1941; 52 (Reel 2)
  June 19, 1941. 1 frame.
- Letter from Philip Ryan, Works Manager, Containing a List, by Departments, of the Number of Male and Female Employees on the Payroll., 1941; 53 (Reel 2)
  July 14, 1941. 1 frame.
- Notice regarding Vacations., 1943; 54 (Reel 2)
- Agreement between the Clum Manufacturing Company and the International Association of Machinists, District No. 10., 1943; 55 (Reel 2)
- Agreement between Perfex Corporation and the International Association of Machinists, District No. 10., 1943; 56 (Reel 2)
  August 6, 1943. 6 frames.
- Agreement between the Rock-Ola Manufacturing Company of Chicago, IL and Lodge 1628 of the International Association of Machinists., 57 (Reel 2)
  August 30, 1943. 10 frames.
- Articles of Agreement between the Dallas Division and the Ordnance Division of Revere Copper and Brass, Inc. and Local No. 477, United Automobile Workers of America, AF of L., 1944; 58 (Reel 2)
  August 18, 1944. 26 frames.
- Agreement between the Fulton Company of Wesy Allis, WI and the International Union, UAW-CIO, Local No. 335 (two copies)., 1943; 59 (Reel 2)
  September 10, 1943. 23 frames.
- Labor Contract between the L.J. Mueller Furnace Company and Local 409, International Union, UAW-CIO., 1943; 60 (Reel 2)
  November 1943. 19 frames.
- Labor Contract between the George J. Meyer Manufacturing Company and Local Union No. 1258, United Steelworkers of America., 1942; 61 (Reel 2)
  August 1, 1942. 10 frames.
- Labor Contract between the George J. Meyer Manufacturing Company and Local Union No. 1258, United Steelworkers of America., 1943; 62 (Reel 2)
  December 1, 1943. 16 frames.
- Unpublished study-Women in Unions in a Midwest War Industry Area, 1943-1945 (continued) (Reel 3)
- Contracts: Contract Reference Material Chart for the Singer Manufacturing Company of South Bend, IN., 1944; 1 (Reel 3)
  February 12, 1944. Includes Data on the Union Involved, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and Information on War Labor Board Case. 2 frames.
- Contract Recommendation Memorandum regarding the Torrington Company, Bantam Bearings Division, of South Bend, IN., 1944; 2 (Reel 3)
  February 17, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 2 frames.
- Bendix Aviation Corporation, Bendix Products, of South Pend, Indiana., 1944; 3 (Reel 3)
  February 10, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 2 frames.
- Bendix Home Appliances, Inc. of South Bend, Indiana., 1944; 4 (Reel 3)
  February 20, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 2 frames.
- Chicago Telephone Supply Company of Elkhart, Indiana., 1944; 5 (Reel 3)
  March 7, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 2 frames.
- Electro-Voice manufacturing Company of South Bend, Indiana., 1944; 6 (Reel 3)
- Chevrolet Commercial Body Company (General Motors) of Indianpolis, Indiana., 1944; 7 (Reel 3)
- Information Concerning All Plants Affiliated with Local 226, UAW-CIO., 8 (Reel 3)
  n.d. Includes Data on Women's Local Union Activities, Union Programs for Increasing Women's Participation in Union Activities, and Attitudes of Local Union Officials toward Continued Employment of Women and Equal Pay. 1 frame.
- Union Programs for Increasing Women's Participation in Union Activities., 9 (Reel 3)
- Attitude of Local Union Officials toward Special Problems of Women., 10 (Reel 3)
- P.R. Mallory and Company, Inc. of Indianapolis, Indiana., 1944; 11 (Reel 3)
  April 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 2 frames.
- American Bearings Corporation of Indianapolis, Indiana., 1944; 12 (Reel 3)
  April 6, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 2 frames.
- Sunbeam Electric Manufacturing Company of Evansville, Indiana., 1944; 13 (Reel 3)
  November 14, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 2 frames.
- Chrysler Corporation of Evansville, IN., 1944; 14 (Reel 3)
  April 20, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 3 frames.
- US Rubber Company of Indianapolis, Indiana., 1944; 15 (Reel 3)
  May 8, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 3 frames.
- Delco-Remy Division of the General Motors Corporation of Anderson, Indiana., 1944; 16 (Reel 3)
  May 20, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 4 frames.
- Guide Lamp Division of the General Motors Corporation of Anderson, Indiana., 1944; 17 (Reel 3)
  May 27, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 4 frames.
- Bridgeport Brass Ordnance Plant of Indianapolis, Indiana., 1944; 18 (Reel 3)
  June 3, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 4 frames.
- West Pullman Works of the International Harvester Company of Chicago, Illinois., 1944; 19 (Reel 3)
  June 3, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 3 frames.
- American Machine and Metals, Inc. of East Moline, Illinois., 1943; 20 (Reel 3)
- Farm Tools, Inc., Vulcan Plow Division of Evansville, IN., 1944; 21 (Reel 3)
- Curtiss-Wright Corporation, Propeller Division, of Indianapolis, IN., 1944; 22 (Reel 3)
  May 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 3 frames.
- Mouldings, Inc. of Indianapolis, Indiana., 1944; 23 (Reel 3)
- Anaconda Wire and Cable Company of Anderson, Indiana., 1944; 24 (Reel 3)
  May 27, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 3 frames.
- Ken-Rad Tube and Lamp Company of Owensboro, KY., 1944; 25 (Reel 3)
  June 7, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 2 frames.
- Cutler Hammer, Inc. of Milwaukee, WI., 1944; 26 (Reel 3)
  June 17, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 66 frames.
- Clum Manufacturing Company of Milwaukee, WI., 1944; 27 (Reel 3)
  June 28, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 3 frames.
- Perfex Corporation of Milwaukee, WI., 1944; 28 (Reel 3)
  July 1, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case.4 frames.
- Square D Company of Milwaukee, WI., 1944; 29 (Reel 3)
  July 1, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 4 frames.
- A.O. Smith Corporation of Milwaukee, WI., 1944; 30 (Reel 3)
  August 5, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 5 frames.
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Company of West Allis, WI., 1944; 31 (Reel 3)
  June 16, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 4 frames.
- Seaman Body Plant (Nash Kelvinator) of Milwaukee, WI., 1944; 32 (Reel 3)
  June 11, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 3 frames.
- Hart-Carter Company of Peoria, IL., 1944; 33 (Reel 3)
  January 7, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 2 frames.
- Studebaker Corporation, Aviation and Automobile Plants, of South Bend, Indiana, 1944; 34 (Reel 3)
  February 8, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 2 frames.
- Vascoloy-Ramet Corporation of North Chicago, Illinois., 1943; 35 (Reel 3)
  December 22, 1943. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 2 frames.
- Tantalum Corporation of North Chicago, Illinois., 1943; 36 (Reel 3)
  November 29, 1943. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 2 frames.
- Cannedy-Otto Manufacturing Company of Chicago Heights, Illinois., 1943; 37 (Reel 3)
- Elkhart Brass manufacturing Company of Elkhart, Indiana, 1944; 38 (Reel 3)
- Missouri Valley Bridge and Iron Company of Evansville, Indiana., 1944; 39 (Reel 3)
  April 21, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 3 frames.
- Bucyrus-Erie Company of Evansville, Indiana, 1944; 40 (Reel 3)
  April 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 3 frames.
- R.C.A. of Indianapolis, Indiana., 1944; 41 (Reel 3)
  May 13, 1944. Chart Includes Data on the Union, Contract Negotiation Points, Plant Practices, and the War Labor Board Case. 3 frames.
- Jambor Tool and Stamping Company of Milwaukee, WI., 1944; 42 (Reel 3)
- United Automobile Workers, AF of L., 1943; 106 (Reel 3)
  September 28, 1943. 8 frames.
- Union Contract between Mojonnier Brothers Company and Local No. 778 of the International Union, United Automobile Workers, AF of L., 1942; 107 (Reel 3)
  July 8, 1942. 7 frames.
- Information Regarding Contract of Local Union 977, CIO of Decatur, IL., 108 (Reel 3)
- United Electrical, Radio,and Machine Workers of America, CIO, Local No. 1105., 1943; 109 (Reel 3)
  October 4, 1943. 6 frames.
- Farm Equipment Workers, CIO, Local No. 107., 1943; 110 (Reel 3)
  October 12, 1943. 7 frames.
- United Farm Equipment and Metal Workers of America, CIO, Local No. 108., 1943; 111 (Reel 3)
  October 13, 1943. 7 frames.
- Electrical Workers, Radio and Sound Division, AF of L, Local B-1031., 1943; 112 (Reel 3)
  October 4, 1943. 7 frames.
- United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, CIO, Local No. 1150., 1943; 113 (Reel 3)
  October 15, 1943. 7 frames.
- International Union of Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers, Local No. 758., 1943; 114 (Reel 3)
  October 5, 1943. 5 frames.
- Machinists Local 1129, Acme Lodge., 1943; 115 (Reel 3)
  September 19, 1943. 6 frames.
- United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, CIO, Local No. 1151., 1943; 116 (Reel 3)
- Series Survey Schedules
  - United Farm Equipment and Metal Workers of America, CIO, Local No. 104., 1943; 117 (Reel 3)
    December 9, 1943. 9 frames.
  - United Farm Equipment and Metal Workers of America, CIO, Local No. 150., 118 (Reel 3)
    n.d. 8 frames.
  - United Farm Equipment and Metal Workers of America, CIO, Local No. 133., 1943; 119 (Reel 3)
    December 9, 1943. 10 frames.